# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the rails db:seed command (or created alongside the database with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   movies = Movie.create([{ name: 'Star Wars' }, { name: 'Lord of the Rings' }])
#   Character.create(name: 'Luke', movie: movies.first)




Question.create(question: "How would you define an empty object called 'monster' using const?", answer1: "const monster = {}", answer2: "const monster = []", answer3: "let monster = {}", answer4: "console.log(‘Hello world!’)", answer: 1)

Question.create(question: "Which element has an index of [3] in the array ['Red', 'Blue', 'Green', 'Yellow', 'Whitesmoke', 'Black']", answer1: "Red", answer2: "Black", answer3: "Yellow", answer4: "Green", answer: 3)

Question.create(question: "Which element has an index of [-1] in the array ['Eagle', 'Fish', 'Bear', 'Chupacabra', 'Crocodile']", answer1: "Chupacabra", answer2: "Eagle", answer3: "Bear", answer4: "Fish", answer: 3)

Question.create(question: "What Ruby language method can you use to get rid of the last element in an array?", answer1: ".push", answer2: ".pop", answer3: ".exterminate", answer4: ".shift", answer: 2)

Question.create(question: "How would you use a ternary operator", answer1: "if (condition) {value_if_true} else {value_if_false}", answer2: "If true: condition ? else {}", answer3: "", answer4: "condition ? value_if_true : value_if_false", answer: 4)

Question.create(question: "What is a boolean?", answer1: "Number", answer2: "Yes/No", answer3: "True/False", answer4: "console.log(‘Hello world!’)", answer: 3)

Question.create(question: "In HTML, what tag can be used to add an image?", answer1: "<image>", answer2: "<upload img>", answer3: "<img>", answer4: "<image src="">", answer: 3)

Question.create(question: "In which HTML element do we out the javascript?", answer1: "<js>", answer2: "<javascript>", answer3: "<scripting>", answer4: "<script>", answer: 4)

Question.create(question: "What is the correct place to insert javascript?", answer1: "The <body> section.", answer2: "Both the <head> and <body> section can be used.", answer3: "The <tail> section.", answer4: "The <head> section.", answer: 2)

Question.create(question: "How would you console.log 'Hello World!'", answer1: "console.log='Hello World'", answer2: "console.log(Hello, World!)", answer3: "Heyyyyyy World", answer4: "console.log('Hello world!')", answer: 4)

Question.create(question: "How can you create a function using the arrow method?", answer1: "() => {}", answer2: "function => {}", answer3: "function() {}", answer4: "fucntion(arrowmethod) {}", answer: 1)

Question.create(question: "How would you write a condition where 'i' is not equal to 5? ", answer1: "(i <= 5)", answer2: "(i != 5)", answer3: "(i =/ 5)", answer4: "(i is not equal to 5)", answer: 2)

Question.create(question: "How can you comment out a line of code in Javascript?", answer1: "#comment", answer2: "function() {commentOut}", answer3: "No Comment", answer4: "//comment", answer: 4)

Question.create(question: "How can you comment out a line of code in Ruby?", answer1: "#comment", answer2: "function() {commentOut}", answer3: "No Comment", answer4: "//comment", answer: 1)

Question.create(question: "Which operator is used to get the remainder of 2 numbers?", answer1: "(num1 * num2)", answer2: "(num1 / num2)", answer3: "(num1 % num2)", answer4: "(num1 - num2)", answer: 3)

Question.create(question: "What Ruby language method can you use to get rid of the first element in an array?", answer1: ".push", answer2: ".pop", answer3: ".exterminate", answer4: ".shift", answer: 4)

Question.create(question: "Is Javascript and Java is the same language?", answer1: "Yes", answer2: "Of Course", answer3: "Duhhhhhh", answer4: "No", answer: 4)

